businessadviceforum.com 2011-05-16

# Must Read: Business Advice Forum - Rules, Disclaimer & Privacy Policy! - Updated 7 April 2011.

> **Business Advice Forum's Commitment To Privacy**  
>  Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
> 
> **The Information We Collect:**  
>  This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Business Advice Forum website. 
> 
> We request that you provide a user-name and email address on our registration page. The user-name you provide is a name of your choosing and does not need to include any identifiable information. We require a valid email address for verification, as part of our methods to prevent forum spam.
> 
> **The Way We Use Information:**  
>  We use the registration information you provide about yourself only to complete your registration. We do not share this information with outside parties.
> 
> We use email addresses to answer the email we receive and to send you Admin emails, related to your Business Advice Forum membership. These emails are infrequent and you should expect less than 15 such emails per year. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
> 
> We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
> 
> Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
> 
> **Our Commitment To Data Security**  
>  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
> 
> **Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**  
>  Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
> 
> **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
>  You can access and amend all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to Business Advice Forum and visiting the [User CP](http://www.businessadviceforum.com/usercp.php). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
> 
> You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
> 
> To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
> 
> **Google Cookies**  
>  We may publish Google ads at some time on Business Advice Forum. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on publisher sites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to publisher sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
>  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
> 
> **How To Contact Us**  
>  Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use the [Business Advice Forum Contact Form](http://www.businessadviceforum.com/sendmessage.php).
